[{"answer": "Thanks for asking it that way.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "In terms of the veracity of Barack Obama's story?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "He did say that in his introduction to his book.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "How much should we factor that in to perhaps some of the things you've unearthed that aren't quite right?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, he says he only changed the narrative -- used composite characters and compressed chronology in order to make the story smoother but in fact he did it for other reasons.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "To retrain is the narrative?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "He's introspective, he's cautious, he's what I call a partisan observer in his own life.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "What is the real Barack Obama like from what you discovered from 350 separate interviews with people who knew him very well?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Did you find him basically an honest man?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Well, it's a different generation.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Would you think he's got a bit of a free pass on that to some degree?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "How did you find the comparison between President Obama and President Clinton, having now immersed yourself in their lives?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't see anything venal.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "If you were thinking about whether to vote for him or not in November, what is the one thing where you thought, you know what, that isn't good?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Well, and a little bit -- you know, it's interesting because he always dismissed his mother as being naive but he came into the presidency with a little bit of naivete in terms of thinking that that grand speech he gave in 2004 bringing the whole country together, which in my book, in my interview, he said that he couldn't find a reason to exist if not for that universality.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "A timidity?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "With an occasional bold action which is also what everybody saw --", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "-- did you see that now in the presidency?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "What I've found that's positive largely is that he is a human being who's growing and learning.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Conversely, what are the big positives that you found are consistent then to what he is now?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Yes, it's good to talk to you again.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Piers, how are you?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, they are certainly significant to the one minor issue, if you will, of whether or not Shellie new about the amount of money that was in the accounts because clearly they show that she did.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "What is your reaction to these transcripts and to the prosecution's position over them?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Like $155.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "OK, so total everything, how much are we looking at?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "There's no question that they were talking in this sort of simplistic kind of code where they were talking about $155 when, without question, they were talking about $155,000.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "I mean is it -- is the reality that they do have hundreds of thousands of dollars?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "No question, they did not tell a complete truth to the judge.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "So I mean if you were putting a prosecutorial hat on, rather your current defense hat, you can see why the prosecution would be pretty agitated, can you?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Absolutely true.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "I mean it doesn't help you, to be brutally frank, does it not, that they appear to have lied in this, because when it comes to George Zimmerman defending himself and saying X, Y, Z, about what happened with Trayvon Martin, there will be critics now, understandably, saying, why should we believe you?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I would tell you that as we know the conversation between client and lawyer are so privileged, but I will tell you this, that I had never asked him a question about that fund because I wasn't aware of it.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "-- that you can believe now what George Zimmerman has told you about, as you say, the more serious issue of what happened that night with Trayvon Martin?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Judge Lester put his neck out for George Zimmerman.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "That he could just be now in jail for possibly up to two years before this come to trial?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, they truly take this very, very seriously.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What was your reaction when you saw the transcript?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "This is what I do for a living.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Are you concerned about serious threats to your life?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "To the extent that I know about, they are good.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "How would you describe their relationship?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "It may be the one strategy they have.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What do you think of that strategy by the defense?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "The witnesses for the prosecution I found them to be very credible.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How credible have you found the witnesses so far?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I think it's very relevant.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "How relevant do you think that could be?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "These are very difficult cases generically to have a client or defendant testifying, because there are so many land mines that are going to occur with the numerous witness who testified.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Would you, if you were defending Jerry Sandusky, risk him on the stand?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Oh yes, I have forgiven them, because America has forgiven me for so many things And gave me so many chances.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Have you forgiven in your mind the policeman that did what they did to you?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Not only an iconic symbol, but I think he actually, unbeknownst to him when he was doing it -- I think he changed this city.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "In many ways, he was this iconic symbol, wasn't he, for race in modern America?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, I think in this country, it's hard to escape race whenever you have a child who's killed by a man who is not an African- American.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Do you believe that in the end it will be seen as a race case, that case, the Trayvon Martin killing?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "You know, I felt bad for Rodney.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How much was it affected by what happened that day, do you think?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "I believe you have an announcement for us?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "I know that you've just been itching for a chance to go back, but do it in a new way, right?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, I actually went to CBS about two years ago and told them that I wanted to come home.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "When did it all start to happen?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "I drink my own urine.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What is the secret to you avoiding the aging process?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I will hit in 2013, the fall.", "docId": "120618pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "When will you hit the airwaves?", "qSentId": 588}]